♪ DOO-BEE-DOO-WAH ♪
♪ DOO-WAH ♪
♪ WHEN LIFE
IS GETTING TO YOU ♪
♪ PUT SOME FRESH
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ LET MINTOS
FRESHEN UP YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ LIFE IS JUST A BREEZE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU STAY
FRESH AND COOL ♪
♪ BECAUSE MINTOS
PUTS THE FRESH IN LIFE ♪
♪ TASTE THAT FRESHNESS.
JUST CAN'T BEAT IT ♪
♪ MINTOS FRESHNESS ♪
♪ LET MINTOS
FRESHEN YOUR LIFE ♪
[Announcer]
MINTOS. THE FRESHMAKER.
THESE COMMERCIALS
ARE STUPID.
THEY CERTAINLY DON'T
MAKE ME WANT A MINTO.
TOTALLY INEFFECTIVE.
MUST KILL
LINCOLN.
♪ IT SEEMS TODAY
THAT ALL YOU SEE ♪
♪ IS VIOLENCE IN MOVIES
AND SEX ON T.V. ♪
♪ BUT WHERE ARE THOSE GOOD.
OLD-FASHIONED VALUES ♪
♪ ON WHICH WE USED TO RELY? ♪
♪ LUCKY THERE'S A FAMILY GUY ♪
♪ LUCKY THERE'S A MAN
WHO'LL POSITIVELY TELL YOU ♪
♪ ALL THE THINGS
THAT MAKE US ♪
♪ LAUGH 'N' CRY ♪
♪ HE'S A FAMILY GUY ♪
♪ [Playing piano]
[Crowd applauding]
AAH!
[Stewie]
BLAST YOU. WOMAN!
AWAKE FROM YOUR
DAMNABLE REVERIE!
[Sighs]
HONEY. I'M DOING
THE DISHES.
A THOUSAND PARDONS
FOR DISRUPTING
YOUR FLATWARE
SANITATION RITUAL.
BUT YOU SEE. I'M
IN SEARING PAIN!
YOU'RE JUST
TEETHING. STEWIE.
IT'S A NORMAL PART
OF A BABY'S LIFE.
VERY WELL THEN.
I ORDER YOU TO
KILL ME AT ONCE!
HONEY. I KNOW
YOU'RE HURTING.
BUT MOMMY HAS TO
CLEAN UP THE HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT?
NO. IT'S NOT ALL RIGHT!
FOR THE LOVE
OF GOD. SHAKE ME!
SHAKE ME LIKE
A BRITISH NANNY!
[Sighing]
OH. MAN.
THIS IS THE LIFE.
HAND ME ANOTHER ONE OF
THEM PAWTUCKET PATRIOTS.
GUYS. I WANT TO SAY
A TOAST TO YOU.
QUAGMIRE. CLEVELAND...
BRIAN.
YEAH. IF YOU GUYS
WERE BEERS.
I WOULD DRINK
EVERY ONE OF YOU.
AND I WISH YOU WERE
BECAUSE WE'RE OUT.
[Laughing]
THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT'S EVEN MORE HUMOROUS
THAN THAT JOKE YOU
TOLD US LAST NIGHT.
OK. SO A JEWISH GUY
AND A CHINESE GUY
WALK INTO
A BAR. RIGHT?
WAIT A SECOND.
JEWISH GUY AND A CHINESE GUY
WALK INTO A BAR.
AND THERE'S A NAKED
PRIEST SITTING THERE.
AND HE...
OH. SORRY. FATHER.
NO. I'VE HEARD THEM ALL.
OH. LOOK AT THE TIME.
I PROMISED LORETTA
I WAS GONNA
TRIM THE HEDGES
AND BE TENDER
WITH HER.
BELIEVE ME.
CLEVELAND.
OUR WIVES NEED SOME TIME
OFF AS MUCH AS WE DO.
THIS IS WHEN
LOIS DOES ALL THOSE
LITTLE THINGS THAT
WOMEN LIKE TO DO.
[Grunting]
[Car horn honking]
I'LL BE ON YOUR
BED. NO CALLS.
HEY. LOIS.
I KNOW. YOU'VE BEEN
BUSY ALL DAY. SO I
TOOK CARE OF DINNER.
REALLY?
ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS GUT IT. CLEAN IT.
SCALE IT. AND COOK IT.
MM-UAH.
PETER. I SPENT ALL
MORNING CLEANING
UP THE HOUSE.
AND IN 5 SECONDS.
YOU TURN IT INTO
LOW TIDE AT THE PIER.
JEEZ. I'M SORRY. HONEY.
I'D HELP YOU CLEAN IT UP.
BUT YOU KNOW HOW LOUSY
I AM WITH HOUSEWORK.
REMEMBER WHEN I
TRIED DOING THE LAUNDRY?
LET'S SEE.
SHIRTS. PANTS...
H-HEY. I'M MISSING
ANOTHER SOCK.
HEY!
WELCOME TO NARNIA.
I'M MR. TUMNUS.
GIVE ME BACK MY SOCK.
YOU GOAT BASTARD!
HEY!
YOU'RE RIGHT. IT'S
BETTER IF I DO IT.
[Stewie]
AH! DAMN IT TO THE BOWELS
OF BLOODY HELL!
THE BABY'S UP.
CAN YOU GET HIM?
OK. I HOPE HE
DOESN'T NEED CHANGING.
I'M A LITTLE GUN-SHY
AFTER WHAT
HAPPENED LAST TIME.
NO. YOU IMBECILE!
THAT'S NOT TALC!
THAT'S PAPRIKA! AAH!
TAKE THAT!
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL DO THAT. TOO!
CAN YOU AT LEAST TAKE
CHRIS TO HIS GAME?
JEEZ. LOIS. I SPENT
ALL MORNING ON A
BOAT WITH MY FRIENDS
DRINKING BEER.
TELLING JOKES.
AND SCREWING AROUND.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
ME TIME?
HONEY. I'M BEGGING YOU.
DROP CHRIS OFF
AT HIS SOCCER GAME
AND COME
RIGHT HOME.
I NEED YOU TO
LOOK AFTER STEWIE
WHILE I'M TEACHING
PIANO LESSONS. PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
HEH. YOU KNOW I SPOIL YOU.
THANKS FOR
THE RIDE. DAD.
ALL RIGHT.
HAVE FUN. CHRIS.
HEY. PETEY!
QUAGMIRE? WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH. YOU KNOW.
SOCCER MOMS!
[Giggling]
ALL RIGHT.
I'D LIKE TO HANG
AROUND WITH YOU.
BUT LOIS NEEDS ME AT HOME.
I GOT BEER.
BOO. LOIS! YAY. BEER!
SHH. SHH. SHH.
IT'S OK. STEWIE.
WHERE THE
HELL'S PETER?
THAT WAS GOOD. REUBEN.
NOW PLAY BRAHMS' LULLABY.
♪ LULLABY AND GOOD NIGHT ♪
ENOUGH! THE ONLY THING WORSE
THAN THE WRETCHED PAIN
IN MY MOUTH IS THE EXCREMENT
SPEWING FROM YOURS!
OH. I WISH I COULD MAKE
THE PAIN GO AWAY SOONER.
BUT I CAN'T
TURN TIME FORWARD.
OH. NO!
PERHAPS I CAN!
OF COURSE! I'LL SIMPLY
BUILD A MACHINE
THAT CAN MOVE TIME!
I SHALL CALL IT...
A TIME MACHINE.
♪ [Discordant note]
E-FLAT. SALIERI! E-FLAT!
[People cheering]
[Peter]
GO. CHRIS!
DADDY LOVES YOU!
I MEAN IN A PLATONIC
WAY. I'M MARRIED.
[Whistle blowing]
HAND BALL!
PENALTY KICK. BLUE!
THAT'S THE 10TH
TIME TODAY!
NICE GRAB.
ORCA.
GET MOBY DICK
OFF THE FIELD
BEFORE HE BURPS
UP A LICENSE PLATE!
EASY. FELLA.
THAT'S MY KID.
NOW APOLOGIZE.
OK. I'M SORRY YOUR
KID'S A BRAIN DEAD
STINKING BLUE
CHEESE FETA!
THAT'S IT!
WAY TO GO. DAD!
YOU HIT MY MOM!
NO. I HIT YOUR DAD.
STAND BACK.
GIVE HER SOME AIR.
YOU MEAN. "GIVE
HIM SOME AIR."
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
SHE'S GOING INTO LABOR.
YOU MEAN. "HE'S
GOING INTO LABOR."
[Baby crying]
WHOOPS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I
PUNCHED A WOMAN.
A PREGNANT
WOMAN.
I JUST HOPE SHE ACCEPTS
MY PEACE OFFERING.
I SENT HER A LITTLE
SOMETHING FOR THE BABY.
♪ [Music playing]
I WOULD'VE BROUGHT
IT OVER MYSELF
IF I WASN'T
UNDER HOUSE ARREST.
YOU'RE JUST FORTUNATE
THIS IS YOUR
FIRST OFFENSE. PETER.
NO KIDDIN'.
COULD'VE BEEN A LOT
WORSE IF THE COPS
KNEW ABOUT THE OTHER TIMES
I BROKE THE LAW.
AND THERE WAS THAT TIME
I TOOK A WHIZ IN PUBLIC.
[Kids laughing]
AND THAT TIME I
SNUCK INTO WIMBLEDON.
[Tennis balls clacking]
HA. ME AND CLEVELAND
ARE GONNA "AMSCRAY."
WAIT. W-WAIT.
YOU GUYS CAN'T LEAVE
ME HERE ALONE.
WHY DON'T YOU
COME WITH US?
I CAN'T LEAVE
THE PREMISES.
THEY'RE MONITORING
MY EVERY MOVE.
[Beeping]
[Peter]
I GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE!
THERE'S MY LITTLE
HOUSE HUSBAND.
IT'S BEEN SO WONDERFUL
HAVING YOU HOME ALL WEEK.
THANKS. HONEY.
BUT HONESTLY I DUNNO
HOW YOU STAND BEIN'
IN THE HOUSE ALL DAY.
I MEAN. I'M SO BORED.
I CAN'T EVEN
WATCH T.V. ANYMORE.
ALL THE SHOWS ARE
STARTING TO RUN TOGETHER.
[Man]
THIS SHOW CONTAINS
ADULT CONTENT
AND IS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY THE LETTER "H".
[Siren wailing]
[Telephone ringing]
AH. HELLO?
[Sighs]
SON OF A BITCH.
I'M ON MY WAY.
SOME POOR BASTARD
GOT HIS HEAD BLOWN OFF
DOWN AT A PLACE
CALLED HOOPER'S.
BERT. I WISH
YOU WOULDN'T
DRINK SO MUCH. BERT.
WELL. ERNIE. I
WISH YOU WOULDN'T EAT
COOKIES IN THE DAMN BED!
BERT. YOU'RE
SHOUTING AGAIN. BERT!
[Sighs]
I KNOW YOU CAN'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT
I'M GOING THROUGH.
ALL THE STUFF
THAT MAKES YOU HAPPY
LIKE COOKING
AND CLEANING.
IS RIGHT IN THE HOUSE
JUST WAITING FOR YOU.
YOU ARE ONE LUCKY...
AH-AH. STOP NOW.
PETER. I DON'T
DO THOSE THINGS
BECAUSE I ENJOY THEM.
I DO THEM BECAUSE
I LOVE MY FAMILY.
[Laughing]
LOIS LOVES HER FAMILY.
♪ LOIS AND THE FAMILY
SITTING IN A TREE ♪
SEE. LOIS. THE GUYS
WOULD'VE FOUND
THAT HILARIOUS.
WHY DON'T I GO
BUY SOME GROCERIES
AND MAKE US A NICE
ROMANTIC DINNER?
LIKE WHEN WE
WERE DATING.
THAT OUGHTA TAKE
YOUR MIND OFF THE GUYS.
IT ALREADY HAS.
I WONDER WHAT
THE GUYS ARE UP TO?
OH. THAT'S NASTY.
WHERE'S THE DAMN
PULL STRING?
AH.
AAH!
HA. YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA
FIND DOWN HERE.
[Barking]
AAH!
[Man]
PETER!
HEY. YOU'RE THE
PAWTUCKET PATRIOT.
VERILY. COME HITHER
AND GIVE HEED.
WHOA. I DON'T
SWING THAT WAY. PAL.
LOOK. I GOT A DATE
WITH MY FEMALE WIFE.
I JUST CAME DOWN
TO GET SOME BEERS.
WHY SPEND TIME
WITH YOUR WIFE?
IF YOU BUILD A BAR
IN THIS BASEMENT
AND STOCK IT WITH PLENTY
OF FROSTY PAWTUCKET PATRIOTS
YOUR FRIENDS
WILL COME DOWN HERE
FOR A BEER AS WELL.
BUILD A BAR!
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WAIT. ONE LAST QUESTION.
IF I WALK THROUGH YOU.
DOES THAT MEAN.
LIKE. WE'VE DONE IT?
JEEZ. WHAT'S WITH
YOU AND THE GAY JOKES?
[Sighing]
PETER. WHERE THE
HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE HAD A DATE.
SORRY. HONEY.
I MUST'VE LOST
TRACK OF THE TIME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU THINK THE
GUYS WILL LIKE IT?
THIS IS WHY YOU
MISSED OUR DINNER?
TO MAKE A BAR
FOR YOUR FRIENDS?
YEAH. ISN'T IT GREAT?
OH. BOY. I FEEL JUST
LIKE TIM ALLEN.
I BUILD STUFF AND I
HAVE A CRIMINAL RECORD.
[Grunting]
[Men laughing]
OK. GUYS. I GOT
ANOTHER ONE.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN PORNOGRAPHY AND ART?
[Snickering]
HERE IT COMES.
A GOVERNMENT GRANT.
[All laughing]
PETER. YOU ARE IN THE ZONE.
HEY. HONEY. YOU
KNOW THOSE
LITTLE CLAM CAKES
YOU MAKE WHENEVER
WE HAVE COMPANY?
I NEED ABOUT
A DOZEN.
ACTUALLY. BETTER
MAKE IT LIKE 600.
THAT'S IT. PETER!
I'M NOT A SERVANT.
AND I'M THROUGH
TAKING CARE OF YOU
AND YOUR BAR BUDDIES!
JEEZ. WHERE THE HELL
DID THAT COME FROM?
WATCH THE KIDS.
I'M TAKING A HOT BATH.
PUT ME DOWN.
YOU BLUNDERBUSS!
HE'S A LITTLE
CRANKY FROM TEETHING.
AH. I CAN FIX THAT.
[Mumbling]
GOOD GOD. MAN!
ONE CAN ONLY
IMAGINE WHAT FOUL REGIONS
THAT FINGER HAS
ERSTWHILE PROBED!
THERE YOU GO.
MY MOTHER USED TO
USE WHISKEY WHENEVER
I HAD A TOOTHACHE.
MY TOOTH HURTS!
[Peter]
THERE. HOW'S THAT FEEL?
WELL. IT-IT'S...
IT'S DELIGHTFUL.
MMM.
[Water trickling]
[Crowd cheering]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
LOIS. YOU ARE A
WONDERFUL WOMAN.
WORDS CANNOT
EXPRESS
THE DEPTH OF MY
APPRECIATION AND
LOVE FOR YOU.
OH. PETER!
AAH!
HEY. YOU MUST BE LOIS.
NO. NO.
NOT SILICONE.
SILICON. AND THE
DESIGN OF THE DEVICE
IS QUITE INGENIOUS
IF I DO SAY SO
MYSELF. MISTY.
WHAT A DELIGHTFUL MONIKER.
YOU SEE. MISTY.
[Snickering]
MY TIME MANIPULATOR
EMPLOYS AXIOMS
FROM THE QUANTUM THEORY
OF MOLECULAR PROPULSION.
I'VE BROKEN MY PENCIL!
I HAVE A BARNEY
PEN IN MY PURSE.
YOU ARE SPECTACULAR!
CHRIS. WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
SORRY. MOM.
I'M GONNA NEED
TO SEE SOME I.D.
CHRIS. GO TO
YOUR ROOM!
HELLO. MOTHER.
CARE TO PARTAKE
IN ONE OF YOUR
OH-SO-EXHILARATING
GAMES OF PEEKABOO?
OH. MY GOD!
MY BABY IS DRUNK!
NO. I'M NOT!
HIM. YEAH. HE'S
A REAL LIGHTWEIGHT.
MEG. TAKE
STEWIE UPSTAIRS.
♪ SHOW ME THE WAY
TO GO HOME ♪
EVERYBODY!
♪ I'M TIRED AND I WANT
TO GO TO BED ♪
JUST THE WOMEN!
PETER. IN THE 17 YEARS
THAT WE'VE BEEN MARRIED
I HAVE NEVER BEEN
AS ANGRY AS I...
WHAT IS MY PIANO
DOING DOWN HERE?
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A CLAM CAKE BUFFET. BUT...
NEVER MIND.
THAT DOES IT. PETER.
EITHER THIS BAR
GOES OR I DO!
LOIS. HONEY. I
HAVEN'T EVEN TOLD YOU
THE OTHER REASON
YOUR PIANO'S DOWN HERE.
I WANTED YOU TO PLAY IT.
YOU KNOW. LIKE IT
WAS AN INSTRUMENT.
I'M TELLING YOU THE
TRUTH. RIGHT. GUYS?
[All agreeing]
COME ON!
OH. NO. I COULDN'T.
WELL. MAYBE ONE SONG.
PRETEND YOU LIKE IT
NO MATTER HOW
BAD IT STINKS.
[Giggles]
♪ [Playing piano]
♪ YOU'LL NEVER
KNOW JUST HOW MUCH ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW
JUST HOW MUCH I CARE ♪
[Man]
YEAH!
♪ AND IF I TRY. I STILL ♪
♪ COULDN'T HIDE
MY LOVE FOR YOU ♪
♪ YOU OUGHTA KNOW ♪
♪ FOR HAVEN'T I
TOLD YOU SO? ♪
OK. GUYS. THANK YOU.
YOU CAN STOP
PRETENDING NOW.
[Man]
ALL RIGHT!
♪ IF THERE IS SOME OTHER WAY ♪
♪ TO PROVE THAT I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ I SWEAR I DON'T KNOW HOW ♪
SING IT. BABY.
BREAKING MY HEART.
SOMETHING TROUBLING
YOU. PETER?
NOTHING. JUST ALL MY FRIENDS
ARE EYE-HUMPING MY WIFE.
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW
IF YOU DON'T KNOW NOW ♪
[All cheering]
WONDERFUL! WOW!
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY
AMAZING.
THE SECOND THAT
SPOTLIGHT HIT ME.
I BECAME A WHOLE
DIFFERENT PERSON!
SILENCE. YOU
CONTEMPTIBLE SHREW!
OH. I BET YOUR GUMS
ARE STILL SORE.
YOU'RE SO OBSERVANT.
AREN'T YOU?
ARE YOU A DETECTIVE?
YES. MY GUMS
ARE SORE!
ENOUGH OF THIS!
I MUST COMPLETE
MY TIME MACHINE.
MOVE TIME FORWARD.
AND END THIS AGONY!
HEY. DAD.
MOM SAYS SHE WAS
REALLY ON LAST NIGHT.
YEAH. ABOUT THAT.
LOIS. SEE. THE GUYS
WERE JUST BEING POLITE.
THEY THOUGHT YOUR
SINGING WAS TOO...
I WAS JUST NERVOUS.
TONIGHT'LL BE BETTER.
TONIGHT? HONEY.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE'S
GONNA COME BACK TONIGHT.
♪ GIMME. GIMME.
GIMME. GIMME ♪
♪ WHAT I CRY FOR ♪
♪ YOU KNOW YOU GOT
THE BRAND OF KISSES ♪
♪ THAT I DIE FOR ♪
OH. THIS ONE TAKES ME BACK.
NOW THAT'S A WOMAN!
THAT'S A HOUSE.
THAT'S A FISH.
THAT'S A BEE!
♪ YOU KNOW YOU
MADE ME LOVE YOU ♪
I LOVE YOU.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
JOHNNY MULDOON.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
[Crowd applauding]
I WAS BORN IN A
LITTLE TOWN CALLED QUAHOG.
[Man]
WE LOVE YOU.
LOIS! WHOO!
[Laughing]
LET ME FINISH
THE STORY. FELLAS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO
BE UP ALL NIGHT.
OR DO YOU?
"OR DO YOU?"
SHE'S A SMOKIN' LITTLE
PISTOL. ISN'T SHE?
ARE YOU A WOMAN?
NO.
MY HOUSE ARREST
IS OVER. BRIAN.
ROUND UP THE GUYS.
NOW THAT I'M A FREE
MAN. WE CAN DO
ANYTHING WE WANT.
THE GUYS ONLY
WANT TO DO ONE THING.
AND THAT'S OGLE
YOUR WIFE.
IF LOIS WERE MY WOMAN.
I'D KEEP AN EYE ON HER.
THEN AGAIN. I'M
THE JEALOUS TYPE.
WOW! LOIS GRIFFIN!
I LOVE YOUR ACT.
NICE MELONS.
LISTEN. PAL...
PETER. I'M HOLDING
MELONS.
OH.
AND HER HOOTERS
AIN'T BAD EITHER!
NOW HANG ON
A SECOND THERE!
PETER. I'M HOLDING
HOOTERS.
SORRY.
NO PROBLEM.
YOUR WIFE'S
HOT!
THAT'S IT! LOIS. YOUR
SINGING DAYS ARE OVER.
FOR GOD'S SAKE. IF I
WANTED TO MARRY LOLA FALANA.
I WOULD HAVE.
LOOK. LOLA. THIS
WHOLE THING
IS JUST GOING
WAY TOO FAST
FOR ME.
[Sobbing]
FOR THE LAST TIME.
I'M NOT LOLA!
I'M LESLIE UGGAMS!
PETER. HAVING ME
SING WAS YOUR IDEA
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
HEY. I JUST WANTED
TO KEEP MY BAR.
I BUILT THAT
THING SO MY FRIENDS
WOULD COME TO
SEE ME. NOT YOU.
IS THAT SO? LET ME
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I LOVE SINGING!
AND I WILL CONTINUE
TO SING! AND...
HOW DARE YOU UPSET ME
THIS CLOSE TO SHOWTIME!
LOIS.
HEY. WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE GOING. BUDDY.
GRIFFIN. I GOT A BONE
TO PICK WITH YOU.
WHOAH. LISTEN. I DON'T WANT
ANY MORE TROUBLE.
THANKS TO YOUR WIFE
MY HUSBAND HASN'T
BEEN HOME ALL WEEK!
THAT SINGING
HUSSY IS DESTROYING
OUR MARRIAGES!
MM-HMM.
YEAH. THEN DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
COME TO MY
BASEMENT TONIGHT
AND DRAG YOUR HUSBANDS
OUT OF THERE YOURSELVES.
MAYBE
WE WILL.
YEAH!
JEEZ. FELLA. CAN'T
YOU TAKE THAT OUTSIDE?
THIS NEXT NUMBER
IS DEDICATED
TO MY VERY SUPPORTIVE
HUSBAND. PETER.
HUH?
HIT IT!
♪ DON'T TELL ME NOT TO FLY
I'VE SIMPLY GOTTA ♪
♪ IF SOMEONE TAKES A SPILL
IT'S ME AND NOT YOU ♪
♪ DON'T BRING AROUND A CLOUD
TO RAIN ON MY PARADE ♪
OH. BOY. LOIS IS
PRETTY PISSED. HUH?
YES. YOUR JUDGMENT LATELY
HAS BEEN RATHER...
YOU HAVE CRAPPY
JUDGMENT ANYWAY.
OH. THIS IS INTOLERABLE!
THIS FOOLISHNESS
IS PREVENTING ME
FROM COMPLETING WORK ON...
EGADS! THE BLUEPRINTS
FOR MY TIME MACHINE!
THOSE ARE FOR
MY EYES ONLY!
THANK YOU.
LOOK EVERYONE.
STEWIE DREW A
PICTURE FOR HIS MOMMY.
NO!
HOLD UP THE PICTURE.
LET'S SEE.
NO! NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
[Cleveland]
HOW CUTE.
IT'S A TIME MACHINE!
NO! IT'S A...
BLAST. WHAT THE DEVIL
DO CHILDREN DRAW?
IT'S A PHEASANT!
A TIME MACHINE. SURE.
HERE'S WHERE THE
FLUX CAPACITOR GOES.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO BUILD ONE OF
THESE OF MY OWN.
I'LL NOT STAND IDLY BY
WHILE YOU ABROGATE MY PLANS.
YOU SHALL RUE THIS DAY.
GO ON! START RUING!
BYE-BYE. STEWIE.
MOMMY WILL BE UPSTAIRS
TO KISS YOU GOOD NIGHT.
BURN IN HELL!
HELL. HELL HAS FIRE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
♪ IT'S GOT STEAM HEAT ♪
♪ I GOT ♪
♪ STEAM HEAT ♪
♪ BUT I NEED YOUR LOVE ♪
♪ TO KEEP AWAY
THE COLD I GOT... ♪
ALL RIGHT.
BREAK IT UP!
WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE?
YOUR LITTLE
PEEP SHOW IS OVER!
WE'RE TAKING BACK
OUR MEN!
PEEP SHOW? I JUST
DO THIS FOR FUN.
LOOK. ALL DAY LONG
I SCRUB AND COOK
AND TAKE CARE OF MY KIDS.
AND NOBODY CHEERS.
NO ONE EVEN
SAYS THANK YOU.
BUT WHEN THE BAND
STARTS PLAYING AND
THE MUSIC'S FLOWING
THROUGH ME.
I FEEL. I DON'T KNOW.
SPECIAL.
I GUESS YOU ALL THINK
THAT'S PRETTY SILLY.
NOT AT ALL.
YOU DIDN'T TELL US
THAT PART!
UH-UH.
PETER. YOU'RE
BEHIND ALL THIS?
YES. AND YOU'LL
NEVER CATCH ME!
[Cackling]
AAH!
I BET HE ALSO
DIDN'T TELL YOU
HE NEVER HELPS ME
AROUND THE HOUSE.
OR TAKES ME OUT
TO DINNER.
OR NOTICES WHEN
I GET MY HAIR DONE.
OH. NO.
THAT'S JUST...
MY HUSBAND'S
THE SAME WAY.
SO'S MINE.
[Women chattering]
WOW. THIS PLACE IS FULL
OF DEAD PIGEONS.
I'M GONNA GO GRAB
SOME OZONE.
HEY!
PETER! THERE'S A
KING IN THE CARDS!
THEY SAW MY BLUEPRINTS!
WHAT A GRIEVOUS BREACH
OF SECURITY!
DAMN! WHAT DO TO?
WAIT FOR IT...
YES!
INSTEAD OF MOVING
TIME FORWARD
TO BYPASS THIS
WRETCHED TEETHING.
IT MIGHT JUST BE POSSIBLE
TO REVERSE TIME'S HEADY FLOW
AND UNDO EVER HAVING DRAWN
THOSE DAMNABLE BLUEPRINTS.
YOU'LL NEVER GET
AWAY WITH THIS!
SILENCE!
OH.
LOIS. YOU MAKE IT
SOUND LIKE I DON'T
APPRECIATE YOU AT ALL.
PETER. WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU TOLD ME YOU LOVE ME?
YOU KNOW I DO.
I WANT TO HEAR IT!
IS THAT WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT?
RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!
HOLY CRAP!
HOT!
[Both]
AAH!
THERE'S NO
WAY OUT!
AT LAST! MY TIME
DEVICE IS COMPLETE!
JUST ONE FINAL
ADJUSTMENT. THERE.
NOW I SHALL NEGATE
EVER HAVING DRAWN
THOSE DAMNABLE BLUEPRINTS.
BLAST!
JEEZ. WE'RE SCREWED!
LOOK. I PROMISE IF WE
GET OUT OF THIS ALIVE
I'M GONNA HELP
OUT AROUND THE HOUSE
AND SAY "I LOVE
YOU" EVERY DAY.
YOU MEAN IT?
I'M A CHANGED MAN.
LOIS. A BETTER MAN.
AND TO THINK.
IF I HADN'T TAKEN
CHRIS TO HIS SOCCER GAME
I NEVER WOULD'VE LEARNED
THIS VALUABLE LESSON.
[Speaking in rewind]
HONEY. I'M BEGGING YOU.
DROP CHRIS OFF AT
HIS SOCCER GAME
AND COME RIGHT HOME.
I NEED YOU TO
LOOK AFTER STEWIE
WHILE I'M TEACHING
PIANO LESSONS. PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT!
HEH. YOU KNOW I SPOIL YOU.
OH. MY FOOT!
I CAN'T WALK!
I GUESS YOU'LL HAVE
TO TAKE CHRIS YOURSELF.
[Laughing]
AHH! MY DEVICE!
MY TEETH!
I'M FREE! FREE!
I CLAIM THIS MOUTH IN
THE NAME OF INCISOR!
I THINK NOT!
[Gasps]
BICUSPID!
WE MEET AGAIN.
HAVE AT YOU!
EN GARDE!
[Groaning]
SHALL WE BITE
THE TONGUE THEN?
ON 3.1. 2...
AAH!
♪ [Theme music playing]